I lost desire, I never meant to leave.
私は欲望を失いました、去るつもりはなかったのです。
I'm traumatized by excessive sympathy.
過剰な同情によってトラウマを負ってしまった。
I kept on loving the people who are wrong.
私は間違っている人々を愛し続けました。
Until, my heart got swept along.
ついに、私の心も流されてしまいました。
Why do I keep on trying?
なぜ私は挑戦し続けるのでしょうか？
I'll just end up lying.
結局嘘をつくことになる。
"Come on!"
"来て！"
Does it matter if it's fake?
偽物でも問題ないですか？
"Come on!"
"来て！"
When it's real, it's just another mistake!
それが現実なら、それは単なる間違いです!
"So why?"
「それで、なぜ？」
Would you hold on 'til you break?
壊れるまで耐えますか？
Why won't you go?
なぜ行かないのですか？
You won't matter anyway.
いずれにせよ、あなたは重要ではないでしょう。
You're seeking answers for the toying you've been through.
あなたは、自分が経験したいじめに対する答えを求めています。
Grasping for proof that's been locked away from you.
あなたから遠ざけられた証拠を掴もうとする。
I was a dream and the one you're looking for.
私は夢であり、あなたが探していた人でした。
But now,
でも今は
I can't love anymore.
もう愛することができない。
If only time could rewind,
もしも時間が巻き戻せたら、
Fix my own broken mind.
自分の壊れた心を修復できるのに。
"Come on!"
"来て！"
Now it's already too late.
今ではもう手遅れです。
"Come on!"
"来て！"
It's time I reached my expiry date!
そろそろ賞味期限が来ますね！
Goodbye.
さようなら。
My mind begins to break.
私の心は壊れ始めます。
And once I'm gone,
そして私がいなくなったら、どうせ
I won't matter anyway.
私は何の意味も持たなくなる。
"Come on!"
"来て！"
Does it matter if it's fake?
偽物でも問題ないですか？
"Come on!"
"来て！"
When it's real, it's just another mistake!
それが現実なら、それは単なる間違いです!
"So why?"
「それで、なぜ？」
Would you hold on 'til you break?!
壊れるまで耐えられますか？
Why won't you go?
なぜ行かないのですか？
You won't matter anyway.
いずれにせよ、あなたは重要ではないでしょう。
OOOOOOOHOOOOOOOOO....
うわあああああああああ……
"come on."
「さあ」
"does it matter if it's fake?"
「偽物でも問題ないですか？」
"come on."
"来て。"
"how i feel is just..."
「私が感じているのはただ…」「
"...another mistake."
…また間違いだ。」
''so i..."
「だから私は…」
"...kept on lying for your sake."
「…あなたのために嘘をつき続けた」
"why won't you go?"
「なぜ行かないの？」 どうせ
You won't matter anyway.
あなたはどうでもいいのよ。
Another Mistake - Available on Spotify, iTunes, Google Play, and more !
Another Mistake - Spotify、iTunes、Google Playなどで入手可能！
Subtitles by aikijoru san.
字幕はaikijoruさん。
god i love you so much jon u do amazing work, literal masterpieces.
神様、ジョン、あなたをとても愛しています。あなたは素晴らしい仕事をしています。文字通り傑作です。
give me ur vocal cords
あなたの声帯をください。
please sub to this bean named jon he deserve
ジョンという名前のこの豆に字幕を付けてください。彼はさよならに値する
bye
さよなら